♪If I am gone from this world,
will the dark night collapse?♪
♪If I never return
to guard by your side♪
♪If I seal away our encounter
and erase all trace♪
♪Like endless snow
falling into the deep sea♪
♪This life is but a fleeting illusion,
yet it gave me courage♪
♪Love is a miracle♪
=Spring Over Phoenix Pond=
(Adapted from Qin An'an's
"Spring Over Phoenix Pond")
=Episode 6=
I pray with a balanced diet in life,
so just please
don't let me marry Qi Zhao.
Our engagement is already set,
yet you're here praying for love?
Is that any of your business?
Wow, that's a guan of money.
Are you that eager to marry me?
I'm praying for the water in your head
to drain out quickly,
so you won't act like a fool all day.
Wait,
what did you say?
Say that again.
I said you act like a fool.
I gave you face today, didn't I?
So what? Come at me.
- You...
- Miss Xiang.
Miss Xiang,
your grandmother is looking for you.
I'll take you there.
Let's go.
Jin?
Jin.
Why are you dressed like this?
I heard you were here praying today
with Miss Xiang.
I...
I just wanted to see you.
Then I am satisfied.
Jin,
don't go.
Zhao,
this might be
the last time we see each other.
Why?
Mother found a group
of crude men from the countryside,
and she wants to marry me off.
Mr. Zheng is already arranging
matches for me.
I have no choice.
Zhao,
I just wanted to see you one last time.
I won't allow it.
I'm going to confront them.
Zhao.
We are only brother and sister.
I am destined to marry someone else.
Brother and sister...
I hate those words the most.
We aren't related by blood at all.
Since we aren't related by blood,
as long as you marry me,
we can be together forever.
Father and Mother won't agree.
Are you willing?
If you are,
I would brave any hardship
to make you my wife.
Young Lady Qi,
I need to go find my grandmother.
The flowers near
the tearoom are in full bloom.
Let's go take a look together.
Who knows what scheme
you Qis are cooking up again?
Miss Xiang,
you overthink things.
It's hot outside right now.
Your grandmother is advanced in years.
The tearoom
is the perfect place to rest.
Grandmother.
Who permitted you to speak to her?
You've only been back for a few days.
What rules do you know?
If you ruin the alliance between
the Marquis Residence and the Xiangs,
can you take responsibility for it?
Grandmother,
why don't we go
to the tearoom to enjoy the flowers?
The scenery is much better over there.
You can also rest and drink tea,
so you won't suffer in the sun.
All right,
let's go.
Come, Grandmother.
Yes, that's right.
Come, let me assist you over to rest.
I'll support you.
Let's go.
Zhao...
Only this way
can we be together forever.
Zhao...
Slow down.
Madam, mind the step.
Alright.
Zhao...
Don't call me Zhao.
Call me...
Call me husband.
Madam,
it seems this room
is already occupied.
Let me take you somewhere else to rest.
Wait.
Zhao, you're naughty.
Call me husband.
Why does that voice
sound so familiar?
Like I've heard it somewhere before.
Husband.
Jin,
I want to be with you forever.
What if it's someone we know?
It wouldn't be good to disturb them.
Let's go, Madam.
- Let's go.
- Zhao, you naughty boy.
Jin,
I want to stay with you forever.
It's Qi Zhao!
Rong...
Madam.
You...
Who is it?
Mother?
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
How could you do such a thing?
Mother,
Jin is mine now.
I want to marry her
with a proper ceremony.
Shut up! Don't even dream of it.
Mother,
Jin and I are really in love.
I never wanted to engage
to anyone in the Xiang family.
Grant us your blessing,
please.
Aren't Qi Jin and Qi Zhao
siblings?
If he breaks off the engagement
with Xiang Rong,
who else would discuss
marriage with the Qi family?
Young Master, stop talking nonsense.
We only came to pray
for blessings together.
What engagement are you talking about?
Rong,
let's go.
What kind of mess is this?
Oh, good Heavens!
What sin have I committed?
You...
It's all because of you,
butcher's daughter...
Calm down, Mother.
Your mother swapped the babies
and took my daughter away.
- Now you come to ruin my son!
- Mother.
They aren't real siblings?
You are ruining my son!
Mother!
You...
Mother.
Mother!
Let me take you back first, Mother.
Careful.
Have you ever heard
the phrase "an eye for an eye"?
Back at the estate,
when you used such despicable means
to humiliate me,
did you ever think
this day would come for you?
Do you admit your mistake?
I did nothing wrong.
Still talk back?
- Do you admit it or not?
- Dear...
I did nothing wrong!
Stop beating him, dear.
Stop, dear.
Zhao is our only son.
You'll kill him if you keep beating him.
Yuan,
tell him.
Tell him what he did wrong.
His Majesty has long
intended to reduce noble titles.
Father sought this marriage
with the Xiangs
because they enjoy the Emperor's favor
and military glory.
Father wants to rely on
the Xiang family's influence
to secure the Qi family's noble title.
Look at what you did.
You broke the betrothal
with the Xiang family
and ruined our family's reputation
throughout the capital!
If the Emperor finds out about this,
we will lose our noble title altogether.
I don't care about the title.
I only want Jin.
- You still talking back?
- Master.
Stop.
Don't hit him anymore.
You'll hurt the young master
if you keep beating him.
Zhao,
lock him up.
Say no more.
Reflect on your actions.
Only release him
when he comes to his senses.
Dear.
Young Lady,
if we just let
Second Young Lady off like this,
won't she try to harm you?
Let her off?
She lost the Qi family's
most precious possession.
I doubt she can even keep her life.
What possession?
You've shamed the Qis.
I cannot let you live today.
Prince Qi.
How dare you poison me?
I treated you with sincerity,
yet you killed me
on the eve of my enthronement.
This time,
don't even think
about escaping my hands.
♪How I wish to hold
onto this fleeting warmth♪
♪How I wish to live
this life only for you♪
♪When memories sink
and the heart settles♪
♪Forgetting life, death,
parting, and reunion♪
♪How I wish to stay
only in the moment with you♪
♪Anchoring myself by your side♪